scdkey.com 2019-05-15

# About Us - SCDKey.com

**Privacy Policy**

scdkey.com respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data. We realize that the exciting growth of the Internet and online services raise questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment of safeguarding privacy to our online and Internet activities. 

In addition to this general online privacy policy, you may receive notice of other terms that apply to particular promotions or services. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

scdkey.com does not share, disclose or sell any personally-identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on scdkey.com' sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non-scdkey.com marketing purposes. Because this information is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. scdkey.com also does not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from children under his age of 13 on Company sites.

**How We Use Information**

scdkey.com uses the personally-identifiable information we collect online principally to provide you with the service(s) you have ordered and to let you know about other offerings which may be interest to you. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services. At any point of time, should you feel the need to opt-out future communications with scdkey.com, options are given within to exclude those communicated messages to you. .

We also provide personally-identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with scdkey.com' services, or with our customers' or others' use of them. 

We have integrated the logo of our partner, idealo (idealo internet GmbH, Ritterstraße 11, 10969 Berlin), onto our website. When you visit our website, information is automatically sent to the idealo server by the browser you are using on your device. This information is collected and then stored on a so-called server log file for 7 days before being automatically deleted. This process requires no intervention from you and includes the following information:

● IP address of the user's computer,

● Date and time the website is accessed,

● Name and URL of the retrieved file,

● Website from where the user came (Referrer URL),

● Browser used and, if applicable, the operating system of your computer and the name of your access provider.

he temporary storage of IP addresses by the system is necessary in order for the website to be accessed. In this regard, the IP address must be stored for the duration of the visit to the website. Storage in log files occurs to guarantee optimal functioning of the website. The data collected also serves to optimise the website and ensure the safety of the information technology systems. At no point is any data stored together with other personal data. The legal basis for this data processing is Art. 6 para. 11point f GDPR.

**How We Collect Information**

scdkey.com collects information online by asking you for it, for example, when you order a service, apply for a job, or respond to a survey, offer or other promotion. A customer's name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are the most important pieces of information, but we might request other information, based on, for example, the service(s) being ordered or promoted. 

From time-to-time, the Company may provide you the opportunity to participate in promotions, contests or sweepstakes on its web site(s). Such promotions, contests and sweepstakes will also be governed by the rules and regulations posted with such promotions, contests and sweepstakes. If you participate, you will be required to register with the Company, which will require you to provide certain Personal Information. Participation in these promotions, contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to register and provide your Personal Information. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as name, shipping address, e-mail address, and telephone number. We will use this information to notify winners and award prizes. Additionally, during your registration process you may opt-in to receiving additional related communications from us. If you decide to opt-in, we will use the information provided to send you communications described throughout this Privacy Policy. 

**Security**

We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the scdkey.com's web site you will need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information.

Email address: **Service@scdkey.com**

Phone number: **+85264531541**

Unsubscription method:

If you wish to unsubscribe to SCDKey, 

Method one: Find and click on the unsubscribe link in each of the promotional email, we will opt you out from the mailing listing without any cost.

Method two：Un-checking "Subscribe to SCDKey Newsletter"checkbox on the registration page
